Guide to the American Institute of Planners Records, 1934-1978
American Institute of Planners Records, 1934-1978
- Series I. General AIP Files
  - AMPS newsletter articles (Box 63, Folder 53)
  - AMPS correspondence (Box 63, Folder 54)
  - AMPS - California correspondence (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - AMPS - Michigan (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Roster (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - School roster (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Paraprofessional planning (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Study Abroad Programs (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - AMPS memos (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - AMPS Bulletin No. 1 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - AMPS - Indian recruitment (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Follow-up letter (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - AMPS - Campaign strategy (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - AMPS - Selecting fund raising chairman (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - AMPS - Chain-call (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - AMPS - Confer-In proposal (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Consultants solicitations (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - AMPS materials (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - AMPS - Hammer's letter to students (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - AMPS Printouts (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - AMPS - Calvin Kythe Associates reports (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - AIP Foundation/AMPS (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - AIPF/AMPS (Box 64, Folder 21-22)
  - AIP - Community Energy Planning - Sessions I and II (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - AIP - Community Energy Planning - Sessions III and IV (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Films (Box 64, Folder 25-26)
  - National Planning Week (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Conference: American Association of State Colleges and Universities - New Directions, New Priorities, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Conference: Down Zoning (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - "Planning in American Cities" exhibit (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Exhibit: "The Shared Environment: Community Improvement by Design" (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - San Francisco urban design film (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Games (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - AIP journal format (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Seminar: National Land Use Policy (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Olmsted Sesquicentennial (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Energy seminars (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - President's Commission on Population (Box 64, Folder 38-39)
  - National Engineers Week - planning, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - AIP - Most recent National Membership Standards Committee (NMSC) agenda and all matrices (Box 64, Folder 41-42)
  - Receiving folder - Committee on Planning Schools - Warren Jones (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - AIP (Box 64, Folder 44-45)
  - Membership growth - graphs (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Registration - New York (411.07) (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - R. Gladstone's projection to, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - HUD contract - technical information exchange (Box 65, Folder 1-3)
  - AIP Foundation (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
  - Taxation (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Public agency lists and summaries (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Geographical distribution of members (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Membership distribution map, 1961 (Folder 1)
  - National Membership Standards Committee (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Guide to Planning Practice - general (Box 65, Folder 10-11)
  - Urban Design Department (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - AIP/EPA/EIS (Environmental Impact Statement) proposal - EPA Control No. R802461, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - AIP/EPA/EIS proposal - application kit for grant, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - EPA proposal (original) (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - EPA 72-1 - background paper (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - EPA noise report to Congress (Box 65, Folder 17-18)
  - EPA Clean Air Act (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - AIP contract activities (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - EPA-Complex Source meeting (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Proposal - Planning Support Centers (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Corresponding Members Women's Rights Committee (Box 65, Folder 23-24)
  - Women in Planning/630 (Box 65, Folder 25-26)
  - Fellowships - Mellon Grant (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Fellowships - Loula D. Lasker (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Foundations (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Student award, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Student award, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Continuing Education programs (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Student award (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Student awards - ballots, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - AMPS dollar distribution (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Committee for Bicentennial of American Design, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
  - Joint project proposal: AIP-ASPO-NAHRO (National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials) (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - AIP/American Society of Consulting Planners liason committee (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - AIP/ALI (American Law Institute) committee (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - ALI (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Developing Countries (Box 66, Folder 7-8)
  - AIP Committee on Planning Practice (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Continuing Education Seminar (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Short course for planning commissioners - Gulf Southwest Chapter (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Social services/Economic Development Department - responses from chapters (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Elections, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Elections, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 16-17)
  - Elections, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 18-19)
  - General correspondence, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - General correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 66, Folder 21-22)
  - General correspondence, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 23-24)
  - Technical Departmental Evaluation (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Technical Departmental Evaluation, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Technical Departmental Evaluation - staff working draft, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 27-28)
  - Technical Departmental Evaluation, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 29-33)
  - AIP Departments (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Planners Roll Call 75-1 to 75-10 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Planners Roll Call 75-11 to 75-18 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - Planners Roll Call 75-19 to 75-22 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - Planners Roll Call 74-1 to 74-9 (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - Planners Roll Call 74-10 to 74-15 (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - Planners Roll Call 74-16 to 74-22 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Planners Roll Call 73-1 to 73-8 (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - Planners Roll Call 73-9 to 73-15 (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - Planners Roll Call 73-16 to 73-22 (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - Planners Roll Call 72-1 to 72-8 (Box 66, Folder 44)
  - Planners Roll Call 72-9 to 72-15 (Box 66, Folder 45)
  - Planners Roll Call 72-16 to 72-19 (Box 66, Folder 46)
  - Planners Roll Call No. 1-8 (Box 66, Folder 47)
  - Urban design draft of by-laws, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 48)
  - Urban Design - petition for the creation of a department (Box 66, Folder 49-50)
  - Urban Design Department general correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 66, Folder 51)
  - Urban Design - formation of department, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 52)
  - Urban Design - memoranda from William Sheveland (Box 66, Folder 53)
  - List for Urban Design Department (Box 66, Folder 54)
  - VII: 528:1 Urban Design Methods Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan and Regional Planning Department, 1969-1973 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - "The Role of Regional Planning", 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Certification of election results, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Metro/regional planning (Box 67, Folder 5-7)
  - Metropolitan Planning Directors Conference (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Environment, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Environmental Quality Department, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - City Planning and Management Department - petitions (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - National Council of City Planning and Management Agencies (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - "Educational Priorities in Comprehensive Health Planning" (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Women in comprehensive health planning project- miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Women - part-time idea (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Registration and leisure, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Women in planning, 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Training program for mid-career women in comprehensive health planning, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - AIP Planning Education Department, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Planning Education Department mailing lists (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Planning Education Department - election of, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Planning Education Department - correspondence (Box 67, Folder 22-24)
  - Planning Education Department - elections, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Planning Education Department - work programs and reports (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Technical departments - transportation, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Proposed transportation department, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Petitions, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 29-30)
  - Transportation department, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT) contract and proposal (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - DOT 1 - mailing rosters for 6 reports (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Metropolitan transportation seminars - Cleveland, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Receiving folder: Division of Professional Standards - William Spangle (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Receiving folder: Committee on Personal Standards (proposed) (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Receiving folder: Joint AIP/American Bar Association Committee - B. Doeble (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Receiving folder: Committee on Professional Registration (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Receiving folder: Joint AIP/ASCE Committee - R. Jones (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Receiving folder: Joint AIP/CSSE Committee - P. Reid (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Receiving folder: Grievance Committee (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Guide to Planning Practice - tax increment financing (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Division of Planning Education (general) - Walter Johnson (reports, correspondence, etc.) (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Receiving folder: Division of Planning Education - Walter K. Johnson (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Interim file: Programs for Planning Students Committee - Robert P. Jones (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Municipal Manpower Commission (Box 67, Folder 46-47)
  - Conference - Manpower paper 1967 (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - Definition of Planning - Dictionary of Occupational Titles (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Civil Service (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Civil Service Planning (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Housing background paper (Box 68, Folder 4-6)
  - Planning Students (Box 68, Folder 7-8)
  - Planning/Network budget (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Student Planning Conference (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Planning/Network budget, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - National Student Steering Committee (NSSC) (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - The Thang - comment (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - The Thang articles (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - NSSC/Housing Association of Delaware Valley (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - NSSC - case to equalize state funding to black colleges (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Student roster (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Sample contracts (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Maps (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - The National Black Planning Network (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - National Training Laboratories (NTL) (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous organizations (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Fairfax County PLUS program (Planning and Land Use System) (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - AIP communications (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Scholarships (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Complimentary registrations (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Atlanta miscellany (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Atlanta services (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Housing - housing shortages (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Planning publicity, January 1983 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Planning publicity, February 1984 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Rotolo, Bill (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Annual report (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Zoning news coverage (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Awards coverage (student) (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Executive directors - pre-consolidation correspondence (Box 68, Folder 36-38)
  - Executive directors - pre-consolidation correspondence (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
  - Membership standards (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Examiner selection, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 4-5)
  - Membership (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Suggestions for examiners (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - National Membership Standards Committee (NMSC) - Item IV (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Registration, 1958-1963 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - AIP "Role and Scope" (Box 69, Folder 10-11)
  - Chapin statement (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Manpower: Doebele testimony (Ribicoff Committee), 1966 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Wil Horst's Edin and manpower study, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - HUD/PORF (Taylor's Professional Organization Representatives Forum) (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Critical Occupations List (U.S. Department of Labor) draft status of planners (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Manpower - "Flynt Letter", 1961 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency - advice on "Planner Shortage", 1964 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Manpower - HUD Division of Manpower and Training (John Huss) (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - 11. Internal Policy Committee 4 - professional status (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Internal Policy Committee 4 - professional status and practice - chairman, Frederick P. Clark (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Policy Committee (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Professionalism, policy, miscellany (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Previous meetings (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Old reports (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Special project - historical notes on membership policy development (2 Edison "Voicewriter" discs) (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Membership, registration, professional development (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - AIP library report (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Ideas and descriptions of professional planning (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Professional development (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Committee on professional status (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - AIP history, professional development (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Professional development (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Development of Professional Affairs Program (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Board Committee - professional development (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Professional affairs (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Background information (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Background information - shortage of planners (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Bill S1922 - Clark audit, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Manpower - miscellaneous papers (Box 70, Folder 5-6)
  - Manpower - planners and the draft, 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 7-8)
  - Planners for Equal Opportunity (PEO) meeting - New York, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - PEO, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 10-11)
  - PEO resolution and Minority Relations Committee, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - AIP Equal Opportunity Committee, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Federal Statistics Users' Conference (FSUC), 1966 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - FSUC, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - FSUC, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - FSUC, 1971-1973 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - FSUC, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Division of Institute Organization - Restatement of Institute Purposes (RIP) - Wetmore amendment (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Wetmore committee - restatement correspondence (Box 70, Folder 20-21)
  - Proposed constitutional amendment - basic material (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Proposed constitutional amendment - comments from members (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Proposed constitutional amendment - comments from chapters (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Proposed constitutional amendment - Committee Council review (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Division of Institute Organization, 1965-1966 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Draft statement on registration, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - AIP position on registration and licensure of planners (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Registration issues - Toronto, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Recommendations of membership (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Registration of AIP applicants (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Division of Professional Standards (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Recommendations of membership (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
  - Manpower - proposed study, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - The Manpower Problem (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Manpower Study (Walter Johnson), 1966 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Manpower: I-G, Personnel Act, I-G, Manpower Act, 1966-1967 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Manpower: OEP (Office of Emergency Planning)/Torpey, 1966-1967 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - "Manpower Needs for Planning for Next Fifty Years" by Jack Meltzer, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Manpower - HUD white paper, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Counseling and screening committees manual, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - New membership policy; chapter handling of associate members application, 1967-1971 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Chapter membership procedures, 1958-1963 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Division of Professional Standards (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Division of Professional Standards (general) - Portland, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - National Membership Standards Committee (NMSC) - personnel, appointments, etc., 1966 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - National Membership Committee Advisory Panel, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Jack Parker study - AIP examinations (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Professional Document No. 8 - comment from individuals, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Professional Document No. 8 - ACSP review, 1963-1964 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Professional Document No. 8 - National Membership Committee review, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Professional Document No. 8 - Private Practice Department review, 1963-1964 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Professional Document No. 8 - distribution for reviews and comments, 1963-1964 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - AIP chapters - reaction of chapters to professional Document No. 8 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Post office and civil service legislation, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Scope of the profession (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - AIP scope (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Planners-in-Charge survey, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 27-30)
  - United States Civil Service 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Material from H. Merrill - early civil service (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Tentative draft of standards for the Landscape Architecture Series, GS-807-0, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - United States Civil Services series, GS 020-0, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Harry Gold - dissertation: "The Process of Professionalization in the Occupation of Urban Planning", 1962-1965 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - J. Vincent Buck - dissertation, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - AIP Committee Council meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Planning schools, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education, 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Division of Planning Education, 1966-1968 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - National membership, 1965-1968 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Division of Professional Standards, 1966-1968 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Program for planning students, 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - AIP/ASPO/ASCP Joint Committee on Education (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Professional registration, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - AIP/ASCE Joint Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Reformulation of "Code of Professional Conduct", 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - AIP/CSSE Joint Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Planning manpower study, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - National "Code of Ethics", 1961-1963 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - "Code of Ethics" student papers from Dutton's seminars, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Division of Professional Standards - reformulation of code (Stollman), 1961-1969 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Receiving folder: Committee on Reformulation of Code of Professional Conduct - I. Stollman, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Code of Conduct revision, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Professionalism, 1954-1967 (Box 72, Folder 22-23)
  - Professionalism, 1965-1966 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Grievance procedures, 1961-1966 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Professional Development Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Assistant for Professional Development recruitment, 1965-1967 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Assistant for Professional Development - Gordon Jacoby (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Professional Development (reports, liason, etc.), 1963-1964 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - United States Civil Service - "Urban Planner" (020), 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - "Urban Planner" announcement (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Federal Urban Planner Supply (salary level adjustment) (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - United States Civil Service "SPS" series (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - United States Civil Service Commission (USCSC) - GS-020-0 reviewers (Box 72, Folder 34-35)
  - Personnel and Civil Service Committee (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Personnel Classification Committee (Box 72, Folder 37-38)
  - Professional Development papers, 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 39-40)
  - Professional Document No. 6 - notes and drafts (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
  - Harry Gold - correspondence and papers, 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - "The Professional Status of Urban Planning" - Professional Document No. 8 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Professional Document No. 6 - comments (Box 73, Folder 6-7)
  - Professional Urban Planning and Related Fields of Practice - Professional Document No. 5, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Licensing and registration (Box 73, Folder 9-10)
  - New Jersey Chapter AIP Registration of Planners - Vol. I, 1957-1958 (Box 73, Folder 11-12)
  - New Jersey Chapter AIP Registration of Planners - Vol. II, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 13-14)
  - New Jersey Chapter AIP Registration of Planners - Vol. III, 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 15-16)
  - Jurisdictional statements from Supreme Court, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - AIP examinations for membership qualifications consultant (Box 73, Folder 18-19)
  - Planning Education at the Unviersity of Michigan - Thomas J. Michalski (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Chapter responses from AIP members to by-law amendment for membership standards (Box 73, Folder 21-25)
  - Board of Governors - individual responses to by-law amendment (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Membership examination - Parker study proposal, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 27-28)
  - Correspondence file - Membership Policy Committee - Parker, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Internal Policy Committee - membership policy (Box 73, Folder 30-31)
  - Professional Document No. 8 - draft notes (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Council of State Sanitary Engineers/AIP proposals (Box 73, Folder 34-35)
  - New folder and application forms (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Grandfather application form - drafts (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - New phase 3 - member and associate member (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - New phase 3 - provisional member (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - New application forms - draft (Box 73, Folder 40-41)
  - AIP membership materials (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - New application forms - draft (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - AIP membership application forms - historical (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Membership application forms (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - National Membership Committee forms development - application forms, other organizations (Box 74, Folder 5-7)
  - Membership form - re-draft (Box 74, Folder 8-9)
  - Parker Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Membership policies revision, April 1964 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Report of Professional Development Committee (Newark), 1964 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Report on review of Professional Document No. 8, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 13-14)
  - Membership Roster 1961/1962 (Box 74, Folder 14A)
  - AIP membership 1964-1965 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - National Membership Standards Committee - standards development application moratorium, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Faust: "An Analysis of Selected Characteristics of the Membership of the American Institute of Planners" Part 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Faust: "An Analysis of Selected Characteristics of the Membership of the American Institute of Planners" Part 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Study of AIP membership and Faust thesis, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Membership survey, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Roster and membership survey, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - membership survey, 1964-1966 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - New York State - Joint Legislative Commission on the Professions, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Clark tax case, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - New York State Tax Commission ruling regarding F.P. Clark, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - New York State Attorney General, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - New York State tax law on business/profession - 401.011, 1956-1961 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - "Role and Scope", 1959 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - General policy, 1959-1960 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Planning Education Report, 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 30)